<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Floating Tools</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="version">Version 2.5.1</string>
    <string name="copyright">© 2025 pandadevs</string>
    <string name="how_to_use_layout">
        The home screen contains buttons to launch the tools. The Stop (red) Button is at the bottom
        right corner. The menu button in to the top right corner. The menu contains How to Use,
        About App, Contact Us and Settings options. On the Settings screen you get options to change
        preferences and give permissions to the app.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_use_permissions">
        In the Settings screen, click on the toggles to grant the permission. Once it is granted the
        toggle will be disabled. You can revoke the permissions through phone settings.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_use_launching">
        <![CDATA[
        Tap the button to launch a floating toggle on the screen’s edge. You can drag it anywhere.
        Tap the toggle to use the tool or perform the action. Active toggles turn their buttons red.
        Calculator and Notepad save your work automatically. Launching the screenshot toggle will prompt
        you to give media projection permission. More usage info and functionality of the toggles can
        be found below.<br/><br/>
        IMPORTANT: For Notepad and Sticky Notes, tap the check button after typing to exit edit mode.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_use_stop">
        To stop a toggle, tap its button again or drag it to the bottom of the screen. You can also
        use the Stop button to close all toggles. Mirror and Sticky Notes have their own close buttons.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_use_tools">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Mute:</b> Mutes and restores media volume.<br/>
        <b>Brightness:</b> Reduces and restores brightness.<br/>
        <b>Alert Toggle:</b> Toggles between Ring, Vibrate and Silent modes.<br/>
        <b>DND:</b> Toggles DND mode on and off.<br/>
        <b>Font Size:</b> Maximizes and restores the system font size.<br/>
        <b>Timer:</b> Tap to start/stop, long press to reset. Allows custom time.<br/>
        <b>Stopwatch:</b> Tap to start/stop, long press to reset.<br/>
        <b>Screen On:</b> Prevents screen from dimming when active.<br/>
        <b>Mirror:</b> Uses front camera to feed to function as a mirror.<br/>
        <b>Flashlight:</b> Turns phone flashlight on and off.<br/>
        <b>Calculator:</b> Opens and closes a basic floating calculator.<br/>
        <b>Notepad:</b> Opens and closes floating notepad.<br/>
        <b>Sticky Notes:</b> Launches new sticky note to the screen.<br/>
        <b>Screenshot:</b> Takes a screenshot.]]>
    </string>

    <string name="about_app">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Floating Tools</b> provides quick access floating tools that you can use from anywhere on your phone.
        Each tool appears as a movable toggle on your screen, letting you perform actions instantly
        without switching apps. You can enable or disable any tool with a single tap, and the app
        clearly shows which permissions are needed for each feature.<br/><br/>
        Once activated, the toggles stay accessible across all apps, making tasks like calculations,
        notes, or screen actions faster and easier. You can stop individual tools by tapping their
        buttons or dragging them to the bottom of the screen, or close everything at once using the
        Stop button. The app is designed to be simple, efficient, and always within reach.]]>
    </string>

    <string name="about_app_future">
        <![CDATA[
        • Customizing tool colors and looks <br/>
        • Diary option to locally save notepad contents<br/>
        • Floating Dock for cleaner user experience]]>
    </string>
    <string name="about_app_foss">
        Floating Tools is a Free and Open Source Software. An ad-free version of this app will be
        available on F-Droid app store. We encourage you to explore open source software and
        support developers!
    </string>
    <string name="contact_us">
        Feel free to reach out to us with any feedback, bug reports and suggestions, or just drop a
        message to say hi! If you are a developer and want to contribute to the project, we
        encourage you to check out our Github repository.
    </string>
    <string name="first_launch">
        Floating Tools needs certain permissions to work correctly. Overlay permission is essential,
        but you can grant all permissions anytime from your app settings and revoke them from device
        settings.
    </string>

    <string name="acknowledgements">
        <![CDATA[
        Ranjun Singh <br/><br/>
        Vedang Gaonkar <br/><br/>
        Saahil Sakordekar <br/><br/>
        Nandan Sakordekar <br/><br/>
        Divya Prabhu <br/><br/>
        Tushar Sakordekar <br/><br/>
        <br/><br/>
        <b>Emotional Support Crew</b><br/><br/>
        Laila (Evil Cat) <br/><br/>
        Simba (Good Cat) <br/><br/>
        Panda (Good Puppy) <br/><br/>
        <br/><br/>
        <b>AI Tools</b><br/><br/>
        ChatGPT <br/><br/>
        Gemini <br/>]]>
    </string>
</resources>